A Guide to the Ticket Stub Collection, 1929-2015
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
The Ticket Stub Collection, 1929-2015
Fairfax County Public Library
MSS 02-11
0.25 linear feet
The Ticket Stub Collection consists of 0.25 linear feet and spans the years 1929-2015 and consists of ticket stubs for local Fairfax County, Virginia businesses.
Virginia Room staff
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None
Acquisition Information
Collection assembled by Virginia Room staff over a period of years
Historical and Biographical Information
Fairfax County Public Library’s Virginia Room has been collecting ticket stubs for local Fairfax County businesses for a period of years. The collection is continuously being added to.
Scope and Content
The Ticket Stub Collection consists of 0.25 linear feet and spans the years 1929-2015 and consists of ticket stubs for local Fairfax County, Virginia businesses. Businesses include movie theatres, drive-in theatres, parks, schools, circuses, carnivals, historic buildings, and other business enterprises.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
None
None
Index Terms
Business enterprises - Virginia - Fairfax County; Drive-in theaters - Virginia - Fairfax County; Motion picture theaters - Virginia - Fairfax County; Parks - Virginia - Fairfax County; Schools - Virginia - Fairfax County; Tickets
Container List
- AMC Hoffman Center 22 Movie Theatre, Alexandria, Va., 2001-2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AMC Tysons Corner 16 Movie Theatre, McLean, Va., 2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Annandale Theatre, Annandale, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Centreville Multiplex 12 Cinemas, Centreville, Va., 1997-2015 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Cinema Arts Theatre, Fairfax, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Fairfax Corner Movie Theatre, Fairfax, Va., 2004-2015 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Fairfax Theatre, Fairfax, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Fairfax Town Centre 10 Movie Theatre, Fairfax, Va., 1995-2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Gala Carnival, Willston and Montgomery Ward Shopping Center, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- George Mason High School, Falls Church, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Great Falls Park, Great Falls, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Hunter’s Lodge, Fairfax, Va., 1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Kingstowne Cinemas 16, Alexandria, Va., 2007-2015 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Lake Braddock Secondary School, Burke, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Lake Fairfax Park, Reston, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Lee Highway Drive-In, Merrifield, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Lee Highway Multiplex Cinemas, Merrifield, Va., 1999-2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Madison School, Falls Church, Va. Oratorical Contest, 1929 April 8 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- McLean High School, Mclean, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Mount Vernon Plantation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Paul A. Milner’s Free Circus, Seven Corners Shopping Center, 1960 July 18-23 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Skyline Six Theatres, Bailey’s Crossroads, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Springfield Mall 10 Movie Theatre, Springfield, Va., 1995-2006 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Springfield Mall Cinema, Springfield, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Sully Plantation, Chantilly, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Sunset Drive-In, Bailey’s Crossroads, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Super 29 Drive-In, Fairfax, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Tyson Twin Theaters, Tyson’s Corner, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Vincent’s Camera Sports and Hobbies, Fairfax, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Virginia City, Fairfax, Va., Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)